J. Peter Lesley Papers 1826-1898 Mss.B.L56
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. General correspondence, 1826-1898 (Box 1)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1871 Nov. 12; Henderson, A. A. (Box 12)
  - C. H. Hitchcock to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Nov. 14 (Box 12)
  - Rufus Ellis to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1871 Nov. 16 (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Nov. 17; Bost, John (Box 12)
  - A. Litton to J. L. Smith, 1871 Nov. 18 (Box 12)
  - J. Lawrence Smith to J. P. Lesley, 1871 Nov. 20 (Box 12)
  - Fanny S. Morland to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1871 Nov. 24 (Box 12)
  - F. N. Dick to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1871 Dec. 2 (Box 12)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1871 Dec. 4; Andrews, Emma B., 1837-1922 (Box 12)
  - F. A. Genth to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Dec. 18 (Box 12)
  - J. Lawrence Smith to J. P. Lesley, 1871 Dec. 21 (Box 12)
  - M. S. W. To Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1871 Dec. 23 (Box 12)
  - C. H. Hitchcock to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Dec. 27 (Box 12)
  - John Tyndall to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Dec. 27 (Box 12)
  - Richard Allen to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1871 Dec. 28 (Box 12)
  - John Jackson to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1871 (Box 12)
  - Letter to Mrs. Susan B. Lesley, 1871 (Box 12)
  - Letter to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1871 (Box 12)
  - Cornelia Loring to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1871 (Box 12)
  - R. Gretlet to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1872 Jan. 1 (Box 13)
  - Mrs. J. E. Caldwell to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1872 Jan. 2 (Box 13)
  - William L. Learned to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1872 Jan. 3 (Box 13)
  - Eugénie Bost to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1872 Jan. 5 (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1872 Jan. 7; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 13)
  - Mrs. Susan Lesley.t Funds for orphans for John Bost..., 1872 Jan. 20 (Box 13)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1872 Jan. 22; Thayer, J. B. (Box 13)
  - Henry B. Brady to J. Peter Lesley, 1872 Jan. 23 (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1872 Feb. 2; Pumpelly, Raphael (Box 13)
  - Ellen M. Rich to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1872 Feb. 5 (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1872 Feb. 8; Andrews, Emma B., 1837-1922 (Box 13)
  - George B. Jewett to Mrs. Baker, 1872 Feb. 14 (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1872 Feb. 21; Henry, Joseph (Box 13)
  - Julia De V. Foulke to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1872 Feb. 24 (Box 13)
  - Eugénie to J. Peter Lesley, 1872 March 2 (Box 13)
  - Ellen M. Rich to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1872 March 12 (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1872 March 13; Brooks, T. B. (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1872 March 18; Hall, James (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1872 March 25; Brooks, T. B. (Box 13)
  - Henrietta B. Haines to Mrs. Smith, 1872 March 27 (Box 13)
  - Elizabeth L. Smith to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1872 March 29 (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1872 April 6; Brooks, T. B. (Box 13)
  - L. Lesquereux to Peter Lesley, 1872 April 7 (Box 13)
  - to Messrs Bradley and others on the Embreeville Iron Furnace properties in East Tennessee, 1872 April 16; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 13)
  - Ellen Chandler to Aunt Susan I. Lesley, 1872 May 5 (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1872 May 8; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 13)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1872 May 18; Clarke, James Freeman, 1810-1888 (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1872 May 20; Brooks, T. B. (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1872 May 20; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1872 May 25?; Hall, James (Box 13)
  - John J. Stevenson to J. P. Lesley, 1872 May 25 (Box 13)
  - W. P. Blake to J. Peter Lesley, 1872 May 26 (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1872 May 27; Hall, James (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1872 May 28; Henry, Joseph (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1872 June 10; Hall, James (Box 13)
  - J. Lawrence Smith to J. P. Lesley, 1872 July 31 (Box 13)
  - Edward D. Cope to J. Peter Lesley, 1872 Aug. 17 (Box 13)
  - O. C. Marsh to J. P. Lesley, 1872 Aug. 24 (Box 13)
  - O. C. Marsh to J. P. Lesley, 1872 Aug. 28 (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1872 Aug. 31; Worthen, A. H. (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1872 Sept. 7, 9; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 13)
  - John Tyndall to J. Peter Lesley, 1872 Sept. 20 (Box 13)
  - Report on the Franklinite range of minerals in Sussex County, N. J., 1872 Sept. 27; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1872 Sept. 28; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 13)
  - John Tyndall to J. Peter Lesley, 1872 Oct. 22 (Box 13)
  - Mrs. E. C. Agassiz to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1872 Oct. 26 (Box 13)
  - C. H. Hitchcock to J. P. Lesley, 1872 Oct. 26 (Box 13)
  - Wolcott Gibbs to J. P. Lesley, 1872 Oct. 29 (Box 13)
  - John Tyndall to J. Peter Lesley, 1872 Oct. 30 (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1872 Oct. 31; Hall, James (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1872 Oct. 31; Henry, Joseph (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1872 Oct. 31; Henry, Joseph (Box 13)
  - F. A. Genth to J. P. Lesley, 1872 Nov. 13 (Box 13)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1872 Nov. 16; Gurney, Ephraim Whitney (Box 13)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1872 Nov. 17; Clarke, James Freeman, 1810-1888 (Box 13)
  - to Mme. Susan Lesley, 1872 Nov. 19; Bost, John (Box 13)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1872 Dec. 5; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 13)
  - James C, Booth to J. P. Lesley, 1872 Dec. 10 (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1872 Dec. 16; Worthen, A. H. (Box 13)
  - O. C. Marsh to J. P. Lesley, 1872 Dec. 24 (Box 13)
  - O. C. Marsh to J. P. Lesley, 1872 Dec. 30 (Box 13)
  - Outline of autobiography, 1872; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 13)
  - Report to Mr. Anspack on the West Buck Mountain, or Robert's Run Coal basin..., 1872; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 Jan. 19; Hall, James (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 Jan. 19; Hall, James (Box 13)
  - Charles Sumner to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 Jan. 21 (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1873 Feb. 7; Hall, James (Box 13)
  - O. C. Marsh to J. P. Lesley, 1873 Feb. 12 (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 Feb. 23; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 13)
  - H. Ware to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1873 March 10 (Box 13)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1873 March 11; Revere, Josie (Box 13)
  - George W. Maynard to J. P. Lesley, 1873 March 17 (Box 13)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1873 March 19; Clarke, James Freeman, 1810-1888 (Box 13)
  - George W. Maynard to J. P. Lesley, 1873 March 20 (Box 13)
  - W. S. Shaler to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 March 21 (Box 13)
  - B. Silliman to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 March 26 (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1873 March 27; Booth, James C. (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1873 March 27; Hall, James (Box 13)
  - to J. P.Lesley, 1873 March 27; Sheafer, P. W. (Box 13)
  - E. D. Cope to J. P. Lesley, 1873 March 28 (Box 13)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1873 March 29; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 13)
  - M. A. C. to Susie I. Lesley, 1873? March? (Box 13)
  - A. P. S. Report on publication of paper by Edward D. Cope..., 1873 April 4 (Box 13)
  - Harriet Ware to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1873 April 4 (Box 13)
  - John L. LeConte to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 April 11 (Box 13)
  - S. M. Hall to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 April 12 (Box 13)
  - O. C. Marsh to J. P. Lesley, 1873 April 20 (Box 13)
  - Edward D. Cope to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 April 21 (Box 13)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1873 April 22; Henderson, A. A. (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 April 25; Hall, James (Box 13)
  - Eugene A. Smith to J. P. Lesley, 1873 April 25 (Box 13)
  - E. D. Cope to J. P. Lesley, 1873 April 26 (Box 13)
  - J. E. Hilgard to J. P. Lesley, 1873 April 28 (Box 13)
  - E. D. Cope to J. P. Lesley, 1873 April 30 (Box 13)
  - Edward D. Cope to J. P. Lesley, 1873 May 5 (Box 13)
  - Joseph Henry, M. C. Meigs, J. E. Hilgard, S. Alexander, G. A. P. Barnard, H. A. Newton, Wolcott Gibbs, Benjamin Peirce, J. P. Lesley... in re International Bureau of Weights and Measures..., 1873 May 7 (Box 13)
  - John L. LeConte to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 May 7 (Box 13)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1873 May 18; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 13)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1873 May 25; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1873 June 4; Hall, James (Box 13)
  - O. C. Marsh to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 June 5 (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1873 June 9; Henderson, A. A. (Box 13)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1873 Jun 15; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1873 June 16; Henderson, A. A. (Box 13)
  - to Thomas Graham on the Hobson iron ore tract, N. C., 1873 June 16; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 13)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1873 June 29; Hale, Susan (Box 13)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1873 June 29; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 June 30; Hall, James (Box 13)
  - Report on the Calidonia Furnace lands in Franklin and Adams counties Pennsylvania, 1873 July 1; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1873 July 8; Fulton, John (Box 13)
  - J. H. Towne to J. P. Lesley, 1873 July 13 (Box 13)
  - to Susy I. Lesley, 1873 July 29; Hale, Edward Everett, 1822-1909 (Box 13)
  - Report on the Huntzinger tracts in the First Anthracite coal basin..., 1873 July; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 13)
  - to William M. Lyon, reporting on survey of Brush Mountain, Tyrone Gap..., 1873 Aug. 2; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 13)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1873 Aug. 8; Hale, Susan (Box 13)
  - Report on the Huntzinger tract in the First Anthracite Coal Field, 1873 Aug. 9; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 13)
  - to Mrs. Susan I,Lesley, 1873 Aug. 19; Hale, Susan (Box 13)
  - W. S. Shaler to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 Sept. 4 (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 Sept. 13; Hall, James (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1873 Sept. 19; Andrews, Emma B., 1837-1922 (Box 13)
  - M. R. Ware to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1873 Sept. 20 (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 Sept. 23; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 Sept. 24; Hall, James (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 Sept. 24; Hall, James (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1873 Sept. 24; Martin, D. S. (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 Sept. 28; Hall, James (Box 13)
  - to J. P.Lesley, 1873 Sept. 30; Fontaine, William M. (Box 13)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1873 Oct. 1; Clarke, James Freeman, 1810-1888 (Box 13)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1873 Oct. 3; Hopper, Rosa (Box 13)
  - William S. Keech to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1873 Oct. 12 (Box 13)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1873 Oct. 19; Hopper, Rosa (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1873 Oct. 23; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1873 Oct. 25; Baird, Spencer Fullerton, 1823-1887 (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1873 Nov. 11; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1873 Nov. 18; Martin, D. S. (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1873 Dec. 3; Andrews, Emma B., 1837-1922 (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1873 Dec. 6; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 13)
  - to J. P.Lesley, 1873 Dec. 11; Henry, Joseph (Box 13)
  - J. J. Mumford to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1873 Dec. 19 (Box 13)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1873 Dec. 20; Hall, James (Box 13)
  - to Susan I. Lesley, 1873 Dec. 21; Hale, Susan (Box 13)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Jan. 2; Baird, Spencer Fullerton, 1823-1887 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Jan. 7; Baird, Spencer Fullerton, 1823-1887 (Box 14)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1874 Jan. 14; Gurney, Ephraim Whitney (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Jan. 30; Hayden, F. V., (Ferdinand Vandeveer), 1829-1887 (Box 14)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1874 Feb. 1; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 14)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1874 Feb. 5; Revere, Josie (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Feb. 16; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 Feb. 18; Hall, James (Box 14)
  - W. D. Crotch to J. P. Lesley, 1874 March 20 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 March 28; Kerr, W. C. (Box 14)
  - to Thomas L. Kane, 1874 March 28; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 March 31; Newberry, J. S., (John Strong), 1822-1892 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 April 1; Winchell, Alexander (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 April 7; Hall, James (Box 14)
  - Henry Wurtz to Peter Lesley, 1874 April 9 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 April 10; Cook, George H. (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 April 11; Fulton, John (Box 14)
  - Henry Newton to McCalla and Stavely, 1874 April 15 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 April 17; Cook, George H. (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 April 20; Worthen, A. H. (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 April 22; Andrews, Emma B., 1837-1922 (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 April 23; Hall, James (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 May 11; Kerr, W. C. (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 May 18; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 May 19; Andrews, Emma B., 1837-1922 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 May 19; Martin, D. S. (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 May 19; Winchell, Alexander (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 May 26; Winchell, Alexander (Box 14)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1874 May 28; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 May 30; Leuffer, George W. (Box 14)
  - Second Geological Survey of Penna. Statement of disbursement of the appropriations..., 1874 May- (Box 14)
  - 1875 Jan. (Box 15)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1874 June 1; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 June 2; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 14)
  - Henry Wurtz to J. P. Lesley, 1874 June 4 (Box 14)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1874 June 23; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 June 9; Hall, James (Box 14)
  - S. Duppa to George R. Crotch, 1874 June 10 (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 June 17; Hall, James (Box 14)
  - Ellen R. Harris to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1874 June 18 (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 June 19; Hall, James (Box 14)
  - Warren Delano to Susie I. Lesley, 1874 June 21 (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 June 23; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 14)
  - William Duppa Crotch to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1874 June 25 (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 June 25; Hall, James (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 June 30; Hall, James (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 June 30; Hall, James (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 June; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 14)
  - William Duppa (?) Crotch to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1874 July 2? (Box 14)
  - William Robert Crotch to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1874 July 2 (Box 14)
  - Mrs. Flora Crotch to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1874 July 3 (Box 14)
  - William Duppa Crotch to Prof. Peter Lesley, 1874 July 4? (Box 14)
  - Kate E. D. Nicholls to Mrs. Lesley, 1874 July 4 (Box 14)
  - Alexander Agassiz to J. P. Lesley, 1874 July 6 (Box 14)
  - Emily Coulden to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1874 July 7 (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 July 9; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 14)
  - F. A. Genth to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 July 10 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 July 11; Hall, James (Box 14)
  - Anna Jackson to Mrs. Lesley, 1874 July 15 (Box 14)
  - William Jenks to Mrs. Lesley, 1874 July 18 (Box 14)
  - Caroline H. B. Laining to Mrs. Lesley, 1874 July 18 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 July 20; Brooks, T. B. (Box 14)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1874 July 22; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 14)
  - ? S. Duppa to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1874 July 23 (Box 14)
  - Kate E. D. Nicholls to Mrs. Lesley, 1874 July 23 (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 July 26; Hall, James (Box 14)
  - Deuzil Ibbetson to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1874 July 27 (Box 14)
  - Anna Jackson to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1874 July 29 (Box 14)
  - W. P. Blake to J. P. Lesley, 1874 July 30 (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 July 30; Desor, Edouard (Box 14)
  - Harriet ware to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1874 Aug. 12 (Box 14)
  - Caroline H. B. Laing to Mrs. Lesley, 1874 Aug. 13 (Box 14)
  - Hannah C. Stearns to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1874 Aug. 25 (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 Sept. 2; Hall, James (Box 14)
  - to Thomas Peter Lesley, 1874 Sept. 10; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 14)
  - George W. Maynard to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Sept. 12 (Box 14)
  - Austin Flint to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1874 Sept. 13 (Box 14)
  - Austin Flint to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1874 Sept. 14 (Box 14)
  - to Susan I. Lesley, 1874 Sept. 15; Hale, Susan (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 Sept. 15; Hall, James (Box 14)
  - to J. P.Lesley, 1874 Sept. 15; Kerr, W. C. (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Sept. 23; Fulton, John (Box 14)
  - to John Fulton, 1874 Sept. 25; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 14)
  - to Thomas L. Kane, 1874 Sept. 25; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Sept. 28; Fulton, John (Box 14)
  - Hannah C. Stearns to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1874 Sept. 28 (Box 14)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1874 Oct. 7; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 14)
  - Hannah C. Stearns to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1874 Oct. 9 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Oct. 16; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 Oct. 20; Hall, James (Box 14)
  - J. H. Huntington to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 Oct. 23 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874? Oct. 29; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 14)
  - to Samuel R.Cassel, 1874 Oct. 30; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 14)
  - Resumé of cost of Survey..., 1874 Nov. 1; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 14)
  - J. E. Hilgard to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Nov. 5 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Nov. 11; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Nov. 13; Kerr, W. C. (Box 14)
  - Delesse to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 Nov. 17 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Nov. 17; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 14)
  - to Ellis Clark, 1874 Nov. 19; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Nov. 22; Hall, James (Box 14)
  - Estes Howe. Events at Phi Beta Metting..., 1874 Nov. 26 (Box 14)
  - to James Hall, 1874 Nov. 28; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Dec. 1; Hall, James (Box 14)
  - F. A. P. Bernard to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Dec. 4 (Box 14)
  - to Mr. Sherlock S.Gregory, 1874 Dec. 8; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 14)
  - to Mr. Hunt, 1874 Dec. 8; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Dec. 9; Cook, George H. (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Dec. 10; Cook, George H. (Box 14)
  - G. C. Broadhead to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Dec. 11 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Dec. 11; Hall, James (Box 14)
  - to Susan I. Lesley, 1874 Dec. 16; Hale, Susan (Box 14)
  - Charles E. Hall to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Dec. 17 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Dec. 18; Cook, George H. (Box 14)
  - to Sherlock S. Gregory, 1874 Dec. 19; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 14)
  - G. C. Broadhead to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Dec. 24 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Dec. 28; Cook, George H. (Box 14)
  - to Ellis Clark, Jr., 1874 Dec. 28; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 14)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1874 Dec. 28; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 14)
  - Ellis Clark, Jr. to J. P. Lesley, 1874 Dec. 29 (Box 14)
  - George R. Crotch to Frank Howe?? Bradley, 1874 (Box 14)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1874?; Dawson, J. W. (Box 14)
  - Work Done by the Survey in the Fall of 1874., Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 14)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1875 Jan. 2; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Jan.3; Hall, James (Box 15)
  - to "My dear Allen", 1875 Jan. 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 15)
  - to the Trustees of the University of Penna., 1875 Jan. 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Jan. 5; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 15)
  - J. Lawrence Smith to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Jan. 7 (Box 15)
  - Kate E. D. Nicholls to Mrs. Lesley, 1875 Jan. 14 (Box 15)
  - S. Thomas Nicholls to Mrs. Lesley, 1875 Jan. 14 (Box 15)
  - to G. K. Gilbert, 1875 Jan. 15; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 15)
  - Henry Morton to J. P. Lesley, 1875 Jan. 18 (Box 15)
  - Maria Revere to Susan Lesley, 1875 Jan. 19 (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Feb. 2; Hall, James (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Feb. 3; Spencer, J. W. (Box 15)
  - B. Silliman to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Feb. 11 (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Feb. 11; Whitney, J. D. (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Feb. 11; Whitney, J. D. (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Feb. 16; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Feb. 17; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 15)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1875 Feb. 18; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 15)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1875 Feb. 24; Whitney, J. D. (Box 15)
  - E. J. W. Baker to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1875? Feb. 25 (Box 15)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1875 Feb. 28; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 15)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1875 March 4; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 15)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1875 March 6; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 15)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1875 March 10; Baird, Spencer Fullerton, 1823-1887 (Box 15)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1875 March 15; Baird, Spencer Fullerton, 1823-1887 (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 March 15; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 15)
  - Rules or directions for collecting fossil plants, 1875 March 15; Leo Lesquereux (Box 15)
  - J. P. Lesley, 1875 March 29; Brush, George J. (Box 15)
  - to Frederick Prime, Jr., 1875 April 9; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 15)
  - to J. Goldschmid, 1875 April 15; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 15)
  - Ch. W. Wendte to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 April 15 (Box 15)
  - W. Duppa Crotch to Mrs. Lesley, 1875 May 1 (Box 15)
  - Catherine Esther Nicholls to Mrs. Lesley, 1875 May 1 (Box 15)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1875 May 2; Whitney, J. D. (Box 15)
  - Kate E. D. Nicholls to Mrs. Lesley, 1875 May 9 (Box 15)
  - Eugene A. Smith to J. P. Lesley, 1875 May 10 (Box 15)
  - to John Peter Lesley, 1875 May 23; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 15)
  - Notes pertaining to a text book..., 1875? May 23 (Box 15)
  - C. J. Norwood to J. P. Lesley, 1875 June 4 (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 June 10; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 15)
  - Anna Jackson to Mrs. Lesley, 1875 June 13 (Box 15)
  - to James D. Dana, 1875 June 14; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 June 17; Hall, James (Box 15)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1875 June 21; Hall, James (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 June 21; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 15)
  - to Messrs Elliott Bros., 1875 June 25; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 15)
  - to Messrs Elliott Bros., 1875 June 25; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 15)
  - to James D. Dana, 1875 June 26; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 15)
  - to Frederick Prime, Jr., 1875 June 28; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 15)
  - Lesquereux, Leo to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 June 28 (Box 15)
  - George F. Barker to J. P. Lesley, 1875 July1 (Box 15)
  - C. J. N orwood to J. P. Lesley, 1875 July 1 (Box 15)
  - to Frederick Prime, Jr., 1875 July 2; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 July 3; Hall, James (Box 15)
  - F. A. P. Barnard to J. P. Lesley, 1875 July 10 (Box 15)
  - Anna Jackson to Mrs. Lesley, 1875 July 11 (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 July 22; Hall, James (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 July 27; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 15)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1875 Aug. 3, 30; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 15)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1875 Aug. 3; Andrews, Emma B., 1837-1922 (Box 15)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1875 Aug. 3; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Aug. 9; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Aug. 15; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 15)
  - to Messts Elliott Bros., 1875 Aug. 19; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lelsey, 1875 Aug. 23; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Aug. 24; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 15)
  - to John H. Dewees, 1875 Sept. 1; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 15)
  - to R. P. Rothwell, 1875 Sept. 1; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 15)
  - to "My dear Hunt", 1875 Sept. 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Sept. 6; Hall, James (Box 15)